[♪♪♪]
PETER:
All right, let's do this one last time.
My name is Peter Parker.
I was bitten by a radioactive spider.
And for 10 years, I've been the one...
...and only...
...Spider-Man.
I'm pretty sure you know the rest.
With great power comes
great responsibility.
I saved a bunch of people,
fell in love, saved the city.
And then I saved the city again.
And again and again and again.
And I did, uh...
I did this.
♪ Get on up ♪♪
We don't really talk about this.
Look, I'm a comic book. I'm a cereal.
Did a Christmas album.
I have an excellent theme song.
♪ Spider-Man, Spider-Man ♪♪
And a so-so popsicle.
I mean, I've looked worse.
But after everything...
- Ah!
- ...I still love being Spider-Man.
I mean, who wouldn't?
So no matter how many hits I take...
...I always find a way to come back.
Because the only thing standing
between this city and oblivion...
...is me.
There's only one Spider-Man.
And you're lookin' at him.
[POST MALONE & SWAE LEE'S
"SUNFLOWER" PLAYING]
MILES:
♪ Oh! Ooh, ohh, ohh ♪
[CLEARS THROAT]
♪ Needless to say, I keep uh, uh ♪
♪ She was all bad-bad, nevertheless ♪♪
RIO:
Miles!
Miles, papá, time for school!
JEFFERSON:
Miles!
- Miles!
- Yeah! Yeah?
Are you finished packing for school?
Yeah.
Just ironing my last shirt.
[RIO SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
JEFFERSON: Come on! You a grown
man now. Let's show these teachers that.
RIO [IN ENGLISH]:
Miles!
Where's my laptop?
If you want me to drive you,
we gotta go now.
No, Dad, I'll walk.
- Personal chauffeur going once.
- It's okay.
[SPEAKS SPANISH]
- [IN ENGLISH] Miles! Gotta go.
- In a minute!
- Gotta go.
- Mom, I gotta go.
- In a minute.
[MILES GROANS]
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
[IN ENGLISH]
See you Friday.
[MILES SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
Look who's back.
Yo, what's going on, bro?
[IN ENGLISH]
Hey, I'm just walking by. How you doin'?
[BOTH SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Yo, Miles!
You feel that earthquake last night?
[IN ENGLISH] What you talkin' about?
I slept like a baby last night.
- How's that new school?
- So easy.
- We miss you, Miles.
- You miss me? I still live here!
Wait, you miss me?
[♪♪♪]
Contra!
[SIREN CHIRPS]
Oh, come on.
Seriously, Dad.
Walking would've been fine.
You can walk plenty on Saturday
when you peel those stickers off.
You saw that? I don't know if that was me.
And the two from yesterday on Clinton.
Yeah, those were me.
Oh. Look at that.
Another new coffee shop.
- You see that?
- Totally. Yeah.
- What's that one called?
- Foam Party.
"Foam Party"? Ha, ha. Come on.
And everyone is just linin' up.
You see that?
I see it.
- Is that a coffee shop or a disco?
- Dad, you're old, man.
WOMAN [OVER RADIO]:
There are multiple reports...
...of another mysterious
seismic event last night.
Sources close to Spider-Man say
he's looking into the problem.
Spider-Man.
I mean, this guy swings in once a day...
...zip-zap-zop in his little mask
and answers to no one. Right?
Yeah, Dad. Yeah.
Meanwhile, my guys are out there...
- ...lives on the line, no masks.
- Uh-huh.
- We show our faces.
- Speed up. I know these kids.
With great ability comes
great accountability.
That's not even how the saying goes.
I do like his cereal, though.
I'll give him that.
Oh, my gosh. Don't cops run red lights?
Oh, yeah, some do.
But, uh, tsk, not your dad.
♪ My memories keep begging
For someone else ♪
♪ I know this feeling, yes
I know it very well ♪♪
Why can't I go back to Brooklyn Middle?
You've given it two weeks.
We're not having this conversation.
- I just think that this new school is elitist.
- "Elitist"?
And I would prefer to be
at a normal school among the people.
"The people"? These are your people.
I'm only here
'cause I won that stupid lottery.
No way. You passed the entry test
just like everybody else.
You have an opportunity here.
You wanna blow that?
You wanna end up like your uncle?
What's wrong with Uncle Aaron?
He's a good guy.
We all make choices in life.
It doesn't feel
like I have a choice right now.
You don't!
[♪♪♪]
[MILES SIGHS]
I love you, Miles.
Yeah, I know, Dad. See you Friday.
[SIREN CHIRPS]
[OVER PA]
You gotta say "I love you" back.
Dad, are you serious?
- I wanna hear it. "I love you, Dad."
- You wanna hear me say it?
- You're dropping me off at a school.
- "I love you, Dad."
- Look at this place.
- "Dad, I love you."
Dad, I love you.
That's a copy.
Tie your shoes, please.
BOY 1:
"I love you, Dad."
Hey, good morning. How you doin'?
Weekend was short, huh?
BOY 2: "That's a copy."
Oh, my gosh! This is embarrassing.
We wore the same jacket.
Hey. Your shoe's untied.
Yeah, I'm aware. It's a choice.
[♪♪♪]
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
Who can solve this for XY?
And that is known as a syllogism.
Read two chapters
of Great Expectations.
A take-home quiz on volumetric pressure.
Five-page essay
with your conclusions stressed.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
WOMAN [ON SCREEN]:
- - countless other possibilities.
There could be a universe
where I am wearing red.
Or wearing leather pants.
Mr. Morales. Movin' in the dark.
You're late again.
Einstein said time was relative, right?
Maybe I'm not late.
Maybe you guys are early.
[CHUCKLES]
Sorry. It was just so quiet.
Would you like to keep standing there,
or do you wanna sit down?
Our universe is, in fact,
one of many parallel universes...
...happening at the exact same time.
Thanks to everyone here
at the Fisk Family Foundation...
- I liked your joke.
- Really?
I mean, it wasn't funny.
That's why I laughed.
But it was smart, so I liked it.
I don't think I've seen you before.
MS. CALLEROS: Shh.
Every choice that we make...
...would create countless
other possibilities.
A what-if to infinity.
MILES:
A zero?
A few more of those, you'd probably have
to kick me outta here, huh?
Maybe I'm just not right for this school.
If a person wearing a blindfold
picked the answers...
...on a true-or-false quiz at random...
...do you know
what score they would get?
- 50%?
- That's right!
The only way to get all the answers wrong
is to know which answers are right.
You're trying to quit.
And I'm not gonna let you.
I'm assigning you a personal essay.
Not about physics, but about you...
...and what kind of person
you want to be.
[TRAIN APPROACHING]
[NOTORIOUS B.I.G.'s
"HYPNOTIZE" PLAYING]
♪ Come on ♪
♪ Hah, sicker than your average
Poppa twist cabbage off instinct ♪
♪ Don't think, stink, pink gators ♪
♪ My Detroit players
Timbs for my hooligans in Brooklyn ♪
♪ Dead right, if the head right
Biggie there e'rynight ♪
♪ Poppa been smooth
Since days of Underoos ♪
[CELL PHONE BUZZES]
♪ Never lose, never choose to
Bruise crews who ♪
♪ Do something to us ♪♪
Uncle Aaron! Hey! Were you scared?
[BLOWING]
[CHUCKLES]
[GRUNTING]
You want that? Huh? Ha!
- What's up with school?
- Going great! Got tons of friends.
You can't tell me it's all that bad there.
Smart girls is where it's at.
Place must be full of 'em.
[AARON CHUCKLES]
Heh, heh. No, there's no one.
Yo, I can't have no nephew of mine
on the streets with no game.
Hey, I got game.
There's a new girl. Actually, you know,
she's kinda into me. You know how it is.
What's her name?
You know, we layin' down
the groundwork right now.
[AARON CHUCKLES]
You know about the shoulder touch?
'Course I do. Heh.
But, uh, tell me anyway.
Tomorrow, find that girl.
You walk up to her and be like:
"Hey."
- Heh, heh. You serious, Uncle Aaron?
- I'm tellin' you, man, it's science.
So walk up to her and be like: "Hey."
No, no, no, no. Like: "Hey."
- "Hey."
- Heh, heh.
No. "Hey."
"Hey." Heh.
You sure you my nephew, man?
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
Is that her?
I should probably go.
Still got a paper to do tonight.
Yo, you been holdin' out on me?
You throw these up yet?
Naw, man. You know my dad. I can't.
Come on.
I got a spot you ain't gon' believe.
Naw, I can't. I can't. Can't.
MILES:
I'm gonna get in so much trouble.
AARON: Hey, man.
Tell him your art teacher made you.
[MILES CHUCKLES]
MILES: How'd you know about this place?
- Did an engineering job down here.
[♪♪♪]
♪ One, two, three, four, five ♪♪
[GRUNTING]
- What's up?
- Ha, ha!
Yeah, man, I knew we were related.
MILES:
Whoa!
Brooklyn!
[ECHOING]
AARON:
There's a lot of history on these walls.
This is so fresh.
[♪♪♪]
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
And now you on your own, Miles.
Whoa, slow down a little.
That's better.
♪ Who's the black sheep?
What's the black sheep? ♪
♪ Don't know who I am
Or when I'm coming so you sleep ♪
See what you got now?
Makin' mistakes is part of it.
♪ And you can't beat that ♪
The real Miles comin' outta hidin'.
♪ You gotta hay?
It's for the ho's ♪
Now you can cut that line
with another color.
♪ You can get with this
Or you can get with that ♪
♪ I think you'll get with this
For this is where it's at ♪
Little help?
♪ Mary who was quite contrary ♪
♪ Talkin' 'bout Mary ♪♪
AARON:
Did you want drips?
'Cause if you do, that's cool,
but if you don't, you gotta keep it moving.
MILES:
That's intentional.
[AARON CHUCKLES]
AARON:
Wow.
- Is it too crazy?
- No, man.
Miles, I see exactly
what you're doing there.
Yeah. You know, me and your dad used
to do this back in the day.
- Stop lyin'.
- It's true.
Then he took on the cop thing,
and I don't know...
He's a good guy, just...
You know what I'm sayin'.
[CELL PHONE BUZZES]
All right, come on, man. I gotta roll.
[GASPS]
Miles, let's go.
[♪♪♪]
[ALARM BEEPING THEN TURNS OFF]
MILES:
That's weird.
My pants shrank.
I think I hit puberty.
[SCHOOLBELL RINGING]
I gotta get new pants.
Wait. Why is the voice in my head
so loud?
What?
- Oh! Are you okay?
- What?
Why am I so sweaty?
Why are you so sweaty?
It's a puberty thing.
I don't know why I said that.
I'm not going through puberty.
I did, but I'm done.
[IN DEEP VOICE]
I'm a man.
[IN NORMAL VOICE] So you're, like,
new here, right? We got that in common.
Yeah. That's one thing.
Cool. Yeah.
I'm Miles.
I'm Gwe... anda.
Wait, your name is Gwanda?
Yes, it's African. I'm South African.
Uh, no accent though
'cause I was raised here.
MILES: Do the shoulder touch now
before she walks away.
Why is this so scary?
Am I doing this in slow motion
or does it just feel that way?
I'm kidding.
It's Wanda. No "G." That's crazy. Heh.
[IN DEEP VOICE]
Hey.
Okay, then. Uh...
I'll see you around.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Oh. See you.
- Sorry. Um...
- Hey.
- Oh, crap.
- Um, can you let go, please?
- I can't let go.
- Ow, ow, ow. Calm down. It's fine.
[BOTH YELL]
- Miles, let go.
- Workin' on it.
It's just puberty.
I don't think you know what puberty is.
Just relax.
- Okay, I have a plan.
- Great.
- I'm gonna pull really hard.
- That's a terrible plan.
- One.
- Don't do this.
- Two.
- Three!
[MILES SCREAMS]
[CLIPPERS WHIRRING]
Nice to meet you?
Sure. Total pleasure.
MILES:
No one saw. It's okay.
No one knows, no one knows.
[♪♪♪]
Everyone knows.
Everyone knows. They're talkin'
'bout me. They saw everything!
He knows. She knows. They know.
Wow, she's super tall.
Why is he smiling? Am I
the weird guy now? What am I doing?
That guy's such a weirdo.
How do I stop?
Can they hear my thoughts?!
Why are all my thoughts so loud?!
Hey! I know you snuck out last night,
Morales.
MILES:
Play dumb!
Who's Morales?
Not that dumb!
Hey!
[♪♪♪]
Okay, okay. You're okay. You're okay.
He'll never find you.
No.
Ow!
What are you doing in my office,
Morales?!
Morales! Open up!
[OVER LAPTOP]
♪ Spider bells, goblin smells ♪
MILES:
Why is this happening?
♪ Spider buggy blew a tire ♪♪
He's got a nice voice.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
GUARD:
Open up!
MILES:
Stop sticking!
[MILES YELPS]
Keep sticking, Miles! Whoa!
[♪♪♪]
[SCREAMS]
...Hofstadter is suggesting...
...is that we...
...look on the...
[MILES YELPING]
Okay.
My room!
MILES:
"Why is this happening?"
"Please stop sticking."
"Please keep st..."
Wait, wait, wait.
How could there be two Spider-Men?
There can't be two Spider-Men.
Can there?
[♪♪♪]
Come on, Uncle Aaron, pick up. Pick up!
AARON [ON VOICEMAIL]: Yo, it's Aaron.
I'm outta town for a few days.
I'll hit you when I'm back. Peace.
MILES:
No. No-No-No-No-No.
It's not possible!
It's just puberty.
It's a normal spider and I'm a normal kid!
Whoa!
All right!
I gotta tell someone.
[LINE RINGING]
[SIGHS]
Okay, you're being crazy, Miles.
You're being crazy.
Find the spider.
You'll see.
It's a normal spider.
It's, like, boring how normal this spider is.
[RUMBLING]
MILES:
I'm right here.
Why is this happening to me?
Slow down! What am I doing?
Way over there.
GIRL:
You're like me.
MAN:
Miles. Look out.
MILES: I don't wanna be a hero.
MAN: Miles.
Whoa!
[GROWLING]
SPIDER-MAN:
Norman, listen to me.
MILES:
Spider-Man?
I cannot let you open a portal
to another dimension.
Brooklyn is not zoned for that.
GREEN GOBLIN:
It's not up to me.
Is that Green Goblin?!
Why won't you quit?!
I guess I like Brooklyn not being sucked
into a black hole.
I think I'm gonna go.
SPIDER-MAN:
Staten Island, maybe. Not Brooklyn.
[♪♪♪]
No! No!
[MILES GRUNTING]
[ROARS]
Whoa!
What now?
What is this place?
[YELPING]
[MILES SCREAMING]
Did you know your shoes are untied?
Uh-huh.
This is a onesie,
so I don't really have to worry about it.
[♪♪♪]
I thought I was the only one.
You're like me.
I don't wanna be.
I don't think you have a choice, kiddo.
Got a lot going through your head,
I'm sure.
Yeah.
You're gonna be fine. I can help you.
If you stick around,
I can show you the ropes.
Yeah.
[RUMBLING]
I just need to destroy
this big machine real quick...
...before the space-time continuum
collapses.
Don't move.
See you in a bit.
[♪♪♪]
How does he do that?
Is it here? No, no, it's here.
All right, folks.
I always get this wrong.
Oh, boy.
Prowler.
Man, I was in the middle of something.
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTING]
I am so tired.
Are you mad at me?
I feel like you're mad at me.
That all you got?
[ROARS]
Aw, so gross.
I should go up there and help him.
Who am I kidding?
I should not do that.
[KINGPIN HUMMING]
KINGPIN:
Watch out. Here comes the Spider-Man.
You like my new toy?
Cost me a fortune,
but, hey, can't take it with you, right?
You came all this way. Watch the test.
It's a hell of a freaking light show.
You're gonna love this.
No! No, don't do this! Stop!
You don't know what it can do!
You'll kill us all!
[♪♪♪]
WOMAN:
I see multiple dimensions opening!
That was three, four
and five separate dimensions.
It's unstable! We should stop.
[YELLS]
Norm, what's your take on head trauma?
[GRUNTS]
I tried to warn you, pal.
Goblin, no! Get him outta there!
[GROANING]
VANESSA:
Wilson! Where are we?
GWEN:
Really weird.
VANESSA:
Wilson!
[♪♪♪]
Hey! Are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine. I'm just resting.
- Can't you get up?
- Yeah. Ha, ha.
Yeah, I always get up.
[COUGHS]
The coughing's probably not a good sign.
KINGPIN:
Find him. Now.
Listen, we gotta team up here.
We don't have that much time.
This override key is the only way
to stop the collider.
Swing up there, use this key,
push the button and blow it up.
You need to hide your face.
You don't tell anyone who you are.
No one can know.
He's got everyone in his pocket.
If he turns the machine on again,
everything you know will disappear.
Your family, everyone.
Everyone.
Promise me you'll do this.
I promise.
Go. Destroy the collider.
I'll come and find you.
[COUGHS]
It's gonna be okay.
KINGPIN:
Tombstone. We're done with tests.
Get that thing ready to go again.
And soon.
Run faster!
These guys are weak.
I'd say it's nice to see you again,
Spider-Man, but it's not.
Hey, Kingpin. How's business?
Boomin'. Ha!
Nice. Aw, that's a no-no.
[KINGPIN CHUCKLES]
This might open
a black hole under Brooklyn.
It can't be worth the risk.
It's not always about the money,
Spider-Man.
[GROANS]
Don't you wanna know
what I saw in there?
Wait.
I know what you're trying to do...
...and it won't work.
They're gone.
[KINGPIN YELLS]
Get rid of the body.
What was that?
Kill that guy.
[♪♪♪]
[GASPS]
[YELLS]
Stop sticking!
MAN [OVER PA]:
Stand clear of the closing doors, please.
[♪♪♪]
Yeah, I think it's a Banksy.
JEFFERSON:
Police! Put your hands up!
Miles? Miles?
Why aren't you at school?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. It's okay. It's okay.
Miles? ¿Qué te pasa?
[♪♪♪]
Is it the earthquake?
Can I sleep here tonight?
Miles. It's a weeknight.
You made a commitment to that school.
He's upset.
Of course you can stay.
- Dad?
- Yeah.
Do you really hate Spider-Man?
[ExHALES]
Yeah. I mean, with a vigilante, there is...
Jeff, mi amor.
What? He asked me. Baby, you know
how I feel about Spider-Man. Come on.
Tú sabes que él te quiere mucho.
That's why he's tough on you.
You know that, right?
Mom, do you ever think
about moving out of Brooklyn?
Our family doesn't run from things, Miles.
Yeah, I know.
JEFFERSON: What's that about?
- He's having a hard time, Jeff.
JEFFERSON: When it gets hard,
that's when he's gotta stick it out.
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪]
WOMAN [ON TV]: We interrupt
this broadcast for a special report.
Sad news tonight.
The hero known as Spider-Man...
...has died after injuries related to another
powerful earthquake in Brooklyn.
Multiple sources are confirming
that Peter Parker...
...a 26-year-old grad student
and part-time photographer...
...operated as Spider-Man
for at least a decade.
♪ I'm not runnin', runnin', runnin' ♪
♪ No, I'm not afraid of the fall ♪
♪ I'm not scared ♪♪
MAN [ON TV]: He is survived by his wife,
Mary Jane, and his aunt, May Parker.
Our hero, Spider-Man, is gone.
MARY:
My husband, Peter Parker...
...was an ordinary person.
He always said it could've been
anyone behind the mask.
He was just the kid
who happened to get bit.
I'm going to miss him.
Yeah.
We were friends, you know.
Can I return it if it doesn't fit?
It always fits...
...eventually.
MARY:
He didn't ask for his powers...
...but he chose to be Spider-Man.
My favorite thing about Peter...
...is that he made us each feel powerful.
We all have powers
of one kind or another.
But in our own way...
...we are all Spider-Man.
And we're all counting on you.
MILES:
They're counting on me.
MAN: Probably not you specifically.
I think it's a metaphor.
[MILES ExHALES]
[♪♪♪]
[YELLS]
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMS]
[BELL TOLLING]
[♪♪♪]
I'm sorry, Mr. Parker.
That thing you gave me, that key...
...I think I really messed it up.
I wanna do what you asked.
I really do.
But I'm sorry.
I'm not sure I'm the guy.
I can't do this without you.
Hey, kid. Ahh!
MILES:
Whoa!
What did I do to him?!
No.
Who are you?
PETER: All right, people,
let's do this one last time.
My name is Peter B. Parker.
I was bitten by a radioactive spider.
And for the last 22 years...
...I thought I was
the one and only Spider-Man.
What a day.
I'm pretty sure you know the rest.
You see, I saved the city,
fell in love, I got married...
...saved the city some more,
maybe too much.
My marriage got testy,
made some dicey money choices.
Don't invest
in a spider-themed restaurant.
Then like 15 years passed.
Blah, blah, blah. Super boring.
I broke my back, a drone flew
into my face, I buried Aunt May.
My wife and I... split up.
But I handled it like a champion.
[SOBBING]
'Cause, you know what, no matter how
many times I get hit, I always get back up.
[CELL PHONE CHIMING]
And I got a lot of time to reflect
and work on myself.
Did you know that seahorses,
that they mate for life?
Could you imagine?
A seahorse seeing another seahorse...
...and then making it work?
[LINE RINGING]
She wanted kids and...
And it scared me.
I'm pretty sure I broke her heart.
Flash-forward:
I'm in my apartment doing push-ups...
...doing ab crunches, getting strong...
...when this weird thing happened.
And I gotta say,
weird things happen to me a lot.
But this was real weird.
[YELLS]
[♪♪♪]
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
Ow!
You see, I was in New York,
but things were different.
Also, I was dead.
And blond.
I was kind of perfect.
It was like looking in a mirror.
I have a feeling that the thing that brought
me here was the thing that got him killed.
You wanna know what happened next?
Me, too.
MILES:
Who are you?
MAN:
What are you doin' over there?
Freeze! PDNY.
WOMAN:
Stop!
[MILES GRUNTS]
Are you kidding me right now?
WOMAN:
Stop! Stop!
MILES:
I gotcha. I gotcha.
MAN:
Hey, kid. Drop the body.
Hey, kid. Get over here!
WOMAN: Come on, now!
MILES:
See you, officers! Heh, heh.
Aw, come on.
[MILES YELLS]
MAN: Hey, kid.
WOMAN: Kid, come on, now!
Put 'em up, son!
[SCREAMS]
Uh...adiós?
[GROANING THEN YELLING]
MILES:
Help! Somebody stop that train!
[♪♪♪]
[SIREN WAILING]
PETER:
Oh, hey. What the...?
Sorry.
I'm gonna die!
MAN [OVER RADIO]: Looks like
a child dressed like Spider-Man...
...dragging a homeless corpse
behind a train.
Whoo! Yes! I didn't kill you.
PETER: Who are you?
- Who are you?
PETER: Why are you trying to kill me?
- I'm not. I'm trying to save you.
[HIP-HOP PLAYING
OVER HEADPHONES]
[BOTH YELL]
MILES:
Hey, maybe you guys can go around?
All right. Thanks, New York.
PETER:
What was that?
Kid electrocuted me...
...with his hands.
- You're like me.
- I got some questions.
[GRUNTING]
Why do you look like Peter Parker?
Because I am Peter Parker.
Then why aren't you dead?
And why is your hair different?
Why are you older?
And why is your body...
...a different shape?
Pretty sure you just called me fat.
You don't look so hot either, kid.
Most superheroes don't wear
their own merch.
- Are you a ghost?
- No.
- Are you a zombie?
- Stop it.
- Am I a zombie?
- You're not even close.
Are you from another dimension?
Like a parallel universe where things
are like this universe but different?
And you're Spider-Man in that universe?
But somehow traveled to this universe,
but you don't know how?
- Wow. That was really just a guess?
- We learned about it in physics.
- Quantum theory.
- This is amazing!
You can teach me
like Peter said he would.
Before he died.
- Yeah. Exactly.
- Yeah, right.
Look, I made a promise to him.
Here's lesson number one, kid.
Don't watch the mouth.
Watch the hands.
Peter, seriously...
[SIGHS]
Trust me, kid.
This'll all make you a better Spider-Man.
[YELLS]
Hey, are you okay?
No, I'm not.
What's going on with your body?
I don't think my atoms are real jazzed
about being in the wrong dimension.
[PETER GROANS]
Look, I'm not looking for a side gig
as a Spider-Man coach.
I got a lot going on in my dimension.
"With great power comes great..."
Don't you dare finish that sentence.
Don't do it! I'm sick of it.
Want my advice?
Go back to being a regular kid.
I don't have a choice! Kingpin's got
a supercollider. He's tryin' to kill me.
- What did you just say?
- Kingpin's tryin' to kill me.
Who cares about that.
Where's the collider?
Brooklyn. Under Fisk Tower.
- Goodbye.
- Where you going?
When it runs again,
I'll jump in and get back to my life.
You can't let them run it.
I'm supposed to destroy it so it never
runs again or everyone's gonna die.
"Or everyone's gonna die."
That is what they always say.
But there's always a little bit of time
before everybody dies...
...and that's when I do my best work.
Aren't you gonna need this?
Aw, you have a goober. Give it.
Wait, no. Not so fast.
He called it an override key.
There's always a bypass key,
a virus key, a who-cares key.
I can never remember,
so I always call it a goober. Give it.
- I need it to destroy the collider.
- I need it to go home.
I'll swallow it. Don't play with me.
- What?
- I said...
The collider created a portal
that brought me here. And I have to get...
- Did you break this?
- No, it broke.
I don't remember what happened.
See, this is why I never had kids.
- Can't we make another one?
- We can't do anything.
Thanks to you, I have to re-steal
what your guy stole from Alchemax...
...and make another one of these.
If I don't turn off the collider
after you leave...
...everyone in this city, my parents,
my uncle and millions of others, will die.
And you're just gonna go home and
leave me here to figure this out for myself?
- You good with that, Spider-Man?
- Yeah.
What are you doing?
Making you feel guilty. Is it working?
How could it...? No. Look at me.
Does it look like it's working?
No. No, it's not...
[CHUCKLES]
Ahh! No! No! No! Do not let him win!
All right, kid. You win.
Come on, we don't have a second to lose.
I love this burger. So delicious.
Mm. One of the best burgers
I've ever had.
In my universe,
this place closed six years ago.
I don't know why. I really don't. Mm!
You have money, right?
I'm not very liquid right now.
- Can we focus?
- Mm-hm. Sure.
- The other Peter...
- You gonna eat that?
I'm listening.
The other Peter said he was
gonna be showing me the ropes.
Wow.
You got any Spider-Man tips
you can tell me now?
Yeah, I got plenty.
Disinfect the mask.
You're gonna wanna use baby powder
in the suit, heavy on the joints.
You don't want any chafing, right?
- Anything else?
- Nope, that was everything.
- I think you're gonna be a bad teacher.
- Uh.
Look up where Alchemax is.
"A private technological campus
in Hudson Valley, New York."
You can teach me
to swing on the way there. Fwsh, fwsh!
[CHUCKLES]
[♪♪♪]
I'm not swinging to the Hudson Valley,
Miles. Not after a hearty burger breakfast.
Keep your legs fresh.
You're gonna thank me later.
♪ I can see a new horizon
Underneath the blazing sky ♪
♪ I'll be where the eagle's flying higher ♪♪
- And it's a no on the cape.
- I think it's cool.
Take that off. It's disrespectful.
Spider-Man doesn't wear a cape.
MILES: How do we retrace Peter's steps?
- That's a good question.
What would I do if I were me?
Got it.
Step One: I infiltrate the lab.
Two: Find the head scientist's computer.
MILES: That lady with the bike is the head
scientist. I saw her in this documentary.
PETER: Cool! Step Three:
I reexamine my personal biases.
Step Four: I hack the computer.
It's not technically hacking.
Not now. I just lost my train of thought.
Step Five: Download the important stuff.
I'll know it when I see it.
Step Six: I grab a bagel
from the cafeteria and run.
MILES:
So, what am I doing?
Step Seven: You stay here.
You're lookout. Very important.
Look, man. You gotta teach me how to do
Spider-Man stuff or I won't be able to help.
Watch and learn, kid! I'll quiz ya later!
Why did I get stuck with the janky,
old, broke hobo Spider-Man?!
That's new.
[CAR APPROACHING]
[♪♪♪]
Kingpin.
What am I doing? What am I doing?
[WHISPERING]
Peter!
Ah! Peter!
- [WHISPERING] What are you doing here?
- Kingpin's here.
Just move over.
You're steppin' on my foot.
Go back outside.
No! I can't sit there and let Spider-Man
die without doing anything about it.
I'm not doing that again.
What?
Most people I meet
in the workplace try to kill me...
...so you're a nice change of pace.
Mr. Fisk! Look at this data.
I know you can't really understand it,
but these are really good numbers.
And I got the password.
Mr. Fisk. If we fire again this week...
...there could be a black hole
under Brooklyn.
You see this? And this?
This is multiple dimensions beginning
to crash into each other.
This is pretty standard
Spider-Man stakes. You get used to it.
Watch this. He's gonna say,
"You've got 24 hours."
You've got 24 hours.
What this means is there could be
a rupture in the space-time continuum.
Ooh. That's bad. Actually, everything
she said was bad. I was lying before.
[♪♪♪]
HEAD SCIENTIST:
Hold on. Let me get you some more data.
- What are you doing, bud?
- I can't move.
Okay, relax your fingers. We don't
have time. Just let go. Be in the moment.
I am in the moment.
It's a terrible moment.
- I'm not refusing.
- No more excuses.
I just need more time.
They're right there.
They're gonna see you.
Miles, you gotta unstick.
What do you do to relax?
Relax. Okay, okay, okay.
♪ Needless to say I, uh, uh ♪
Oh, for crying out loud.
♪ Calling it quits
Now, baby, I'm a wreck ♪
[HUMMING]
♪ Ooh ♪♪
Ahh!
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Teenagers: just the worst.
Miles, where did you go?
MILES: I'm right here.
- Where? I can't see ya.
- I'm right in front of you.
- Can Spider-Man turn invisible?
- Not in my universe.
You just poked me in my eye!
This is incredible.
Some kind of fight or flight thing.
What's that?
Remember this password.
D-g-f-a-m-p-e-s-a-n-d...
Slow down!
...-4-$-3-5-8-7-6-5-3-4-5-4-5-3-5.
- I need to write it down!
- Download the schematic.
- How do I do that?
- While I turn on the charm.
Spider-Man?
- Oh, hey. Didn't see you there.
- Wow!
Okay, I'm kinda freaking out right now.
You're supposed to be dead.
Surprise! Okay. That's a no-no.
We don't like that.
This is fascinating.
Okay, that's my face.
An entirely different Peter Parker.
Little bit of a gut,
perhaps from dimensional warping.
Oh, yeah-yeah-yeah.
I was way flatter before I warped.
Travel through the multiverse appears
to have deteriorated the...
MILES:
What was the rest?!
Hey, how old are you?
'Cause you don't look a day over 35.
HEAD SCIENTIST: They said
I was crazy! They said I was crazy!
PETER:
You showed 'em you're not crazy.
This might pinch a little.
- Ow! Ow!
- I know. I just need to get these samples.
Okay.
MILES:
Organize your desktop, lady.
Wow. Just complete cellular decay.
- I've never seen anything like this.
- [WHISPERING] What are you doing?
MILES:
I'm just taking the whole thing.
And obviously you've been glitching.
[IN NORMAL VOICE] "Glitchin""? No.
Why would you even say that?
If you stay in this dimension too long,
your body's gonna disintegrate.
Do you know how painful
that would be, Peter Parker?
I don't know.
You can't imagine.
And I, for one...
...can't wait to watch.
What did you say your name was?
Dr. Olivia Octavius.
[♪♪♪]
Can I assume
that your friends call you Doc Ock?
My friends actually call me Liv.
My enemies call me Doc Ock.
I got this! Run!
DOC OCK:
Who are you talking to?
PETER: I got it!
DOC OCK: Oh, you "got it," Peter?
PETER:
I got it handled, buddy!
Everything is fine!
Okay, this is a little bit bad.
DOC OCK: You're chatty.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Gotta go.
This is the moment
that I'm losin' the fight.
Let me tell you the good news.
We don't need the monitor.
Oh!
DOC OCK: Peter!
You didn't tell me
you had an invisible friend!
Could you give me that back,
young man?
MILES:
Peter!
It's proprietary.
PETER:
Oh!
- This'd be a good time to turn invisible.
- Yep.
Okay, not gonna turn invisible.
Selecting a bagel.
Act super normal.
Spider-Man?
- You know, that's funny, I get that a lot.
- Hey.
- Spider-Man?
- Hey! Hands up!
Now we do a switchy-switchy.
WOMAN: Get back here!
Where do you think you're going?
He took a bagel!
- Time to swing, just like I taught ya.
- When did you teach me that?
I didn't. It's a little joke for team-building.
Hey!
- All right, you ready?
- Of course I'm not ready! Oh! Oh, oh!
I can't do this yet!
Everybody knows
that the best way to learn...
...is under intense
life-threatening pressure.
Ow!
Come on, come on, come on.
Uh-oh.
[♪♪♪]
PETER:
What are you doing down there?
I run better than I swing.
You gotta swing or they'll catch you.
This is what you wanted.
Uh-oh.
Aha!
[GASPS]
Come back, little boy.
Aim with your hips!
Look where you want it to hit.
Square your shoulders.
Don't forget to follow through!
Don't shoot off your back foot.
- That's too many things!
- Then stop listening to me!
That's the best idea you've had all day!
Nice, Miles!
- Ha, ha!
- Good. You're doin' it.
Double tap to release
and thwip it out again.
Thwip and release.
And thwip. Release. Thwip.
MILES: And release.
PETER:
You're a natural. Thwip. Release.
- Feel the rhythm?
- Whoo-hoo! Thwip. And release!
- Good, Miles.
- I gotta say, you're amazing, man.
We're a little team!
Me as the teacher who could still do it.
You as the student who can do it,
just not as good.
I'm proud of us. Is there something
you want to say to me?
Peter!
What the...?
PETER: Who did that?
[DOC OCK GRUNTS]
Hey, guys.
Gwanda?
It's Gwen, actually.
Oh, you know her. Very cool.
I'm from another dimension.
I mean, another-another dimension.
GWEN: All right, people. Let's start
at the beginning one last time.
My name is Gwen Stacy.
I was bitten by a radioactive spider.
And for the last two years, I've been
the one and only Spider-Woman.
You guys know the rest.
I joined a band.
Saved my dad.
I couldn't save my best friend...
...Peter Parker...
...so now I save everyone else.
And I don't do friends anymore...
...just to avoid any distractions.
And one day this weird thing happened.
And I mean, like, really weird.
I was blown into last week.
Literally.
I landed in New York,
but not my New York.
WOMAN [ON SCREEN]: Lucky for these
folks, Spider-Man saved the day.
GWEN: My Spider-sense told me
to head to Visions Academy.
...you guys are early.
Wasn't sure why until I met you.
Oh.
I like your haircut.
You don't get to like my haircut.
Let's go.
How many more Spider-People
are there?
Save it for Comic-Con.
What's Comic-Con?
Whoa!
[♪♪♪]
KINGPIN:
You're dead, Spider-Man.
Wilson! What are you doing?
Vanessa.
VANESSA:
Richard, come on.
Vanessa! Richard!
No!
Don't look back, honey.
It's okay. It's okay.
[HORN HONKING]
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
I killed Spider-Man.
Why did I just see two more?
There's three, actually.
No, this is good. This is very, very good.
This means you get what you want.
It means my collider works.
All we have to do is kill
a couple of Spiders.
And the collider will bring
your family back.
As many families as you want.
Tomorrow, at my collider.
Our collider.
He broke this?
Yeah. He's actually really embarrassed
about it, so just keep it between us, okay?
[CHUCKLES]
I know where we can make a new one.
And we won't let him break it this time.
I'm sorry about your friend.
Thanks, Miles.
I know how hard this is. To have
to figure this stuff out on your own.
It's kinda nice not being
the only Spider-person around.
Yeah.
If you ever decide to do friends again,
I could always open up a slot.
I'll keep you posted.
MILES:
Cool.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
We should probably go.
Peter, we're literally on the doorstep.
PETER: Bad idea. This is a bad idea.
GWEN: Just relax.
MAY: You guys are all very sweet,
but no more fans today, please.
I'm not ready for this.
[♪♪♪]
Peter?
Hey, Aunt May.
So this is gonna sound crazy,
but I'm pretty sure that I'm from an...
An alternate dimension.
Yeah.
You look tired, Peter.
Well, I am tired.
- And older. And thicker.
- Yeah. I've heard that already.
Oh, jeez. Are those sweatpants?
Yup, that's what they are.
I was there...
...when it all happened.
I am so sorry.
And what dimension are you from?
Brooklyn.
Did Peter have a place where we could
make another one of these?
MAY:
A goober.
Follow me.
[♪♪♪]
Oh, yeah, I got one of these, too. A little,
old shed where I keep my Spider-gear.
[POWERING UP]
I mean, this place is pretentious.
Whoa.
Dude. Was yours anything like this?
Mine was like this,
but take away the jeep, the plane.
Imagine it way smaller. Imagine a futon.
I feel sad for this guy.
Hey, Peter.
I think this is a cape.
Peter knew how dangerous the job was.
But he figured the only one
who could stop this guy was Spider-Man.
Kingpin knows we're coming.
We're going to be outnumbered.
Don't be so sure.
You might need these.
[♪♪♪]
You think you're the only people
who thought to come here?
Hey, fellas.
Is he in black and white?
Where's that wind coming from?
We're in a basement.
Wherever I go, the wind follows.
And the wind, it smells like rain.
Hi, guys!
[SPEAKS IN JAPANESE]
This could literally not get any weirder.
It can get weirder.
I just washed my hands.
That's why they're wet.
No other reason.
ALL:
You're like me.
My name is Peter Parker.
My name is Peni Parker.
My name is Peter Porker.
NOIR: I was bitten by a radioactive spider.
- I was bitten by a radioactive pig.
NOIR: In my universe, it's 1933,
and I'm a private eye.
I like to drink egg creams,
and I like to fight Nazis. A lot.
PENI:
I'm from New York in the year 3145.
I have a psychic link with a spider
who lives inside my father's robot.
And we're best friends. Forever.
Sometimes I let matches burn down
to my fingertips...
...just to feel something, anything. Aw.
PORKER: I'm a photographer
for the Daily Beagle.
When I'm not pooching around,
I'm working like a dog...
...trying to sniff out the latest story.
♪ I frolic and I dance
And I do this with my pants ♪
Okay! Enough!
So, uh, how did you get here?
Well, it's kind of a long story.
Maybe not that long.
And now we're just trying
to find a way home.
The only way home is back through
that collider gizmo. The only trouble is...
One of us has to stay behind
and destroy it.
ALL:
I'll do it.
No, no, no. You guys don't get it.
Don't get what?
[ALL GRUNTING]
None of you can stay here.
If you stay here, you'll die.
I'm the guy who's gonna turn it off.
And I'm gonna get you all home
before I do.
Look, I made a promise.
So I have to keep it.
[♪♪♪]
Who are you again?
This is Miles.
- And he's gonna save the multiverse.
- Yeah, man.
This kid can turn himself invisible.
Watch this. He can do it now.
[GRUNTS]
- I can't do it on command.
- He can't do it on command.
But it is cool.
Show 'em the zappy thing, Miles.
[GRUNTS]
- Can't do it on command.
- He can't do it on command.
But he can do so much more.
What else do you do?
- Just those two things.
NOIR:
Aw, man.
Look, I've seen him in action.
He's got potential.
I think he's gonna get us home.
Okay, little fella, Kingpin's gonna send
a lot of mugs after ya.
I'm talkin' hard boys, real biscuit boxers.
Can you fight them all off at once?
I haven't actually fought anyone.
Surprise attack!
Can you rewire a mainframe
while being shot at?
Can I what?
- Show me!
- Surprise attack!
Can you swing and flip with the grace
of a trained dancer?
Can you close off your feelings
so you don't get crippled...
...by the moral ambiguity
of your violent actions?
Can you help your aunt create
an online dating profile...
...so she can get out
of the dang house once in a while?
Can you float through the air
when you smell a delicious pie?
- Can you be strong?
- Ruthless?
- Disciplined?
- I don't know. Maybe.
- Psychic?
- Show me some moxie, soldier!
Above all, no matter how many times
you get hit, can you get back up?
NOIR: 'Cause when a Spider-Man
is on the floor...
PORKER:
When you think you can't keep goin'...
GWEN: Come on, Miles.
PENI: Come on. You can do it.
GWEN: You can do this.
- Guys, cool it.
- Come on. You can do it!
- Get up, Miles.
Come on, Miles. Get up.
You need to be more honest
with yourself about this.
He's not ready. It's obvious.
NOIR: There's no way. He's just a kid.
GWEN: If he can't do this,
we have to stay and do it for him.
He's looking right at us
while we talk about him.
[CLANKING]
Miles? Miles?
You see that? He can, uh...
He can turn invisible.
[♪♪♪]
♪ When it gets dark outside ♪
♪ In you I confide ♪
♪ You help me face my demons
I won't hide ♪
JEFFERSON:
Miles, what is going on with you?
Nobody's heard from you.
We don't know what's going on.
If you're hidin' something from us,
you need to come clean.
You call me back. Now.
He's not answering me either.
It's Aaron. I'm outta town for a few days.
I'll hit you when I'm back. Peace.
Aaron, it's Jeff.
Look, I need you to call me
if you've heard from Miles.
He has a...
He has a soft spot for you...
...and we haven't heard from him.
And you know I wouldn't reach out
if this wasn't important.
Hope you're good.
MILES:
Dear Uncle Aaron.
I gotta do something,
and I don't know if I can do it.
I'm scared, man.
I'm just tired of lettin' everybody down.
You're the only one I can talk to.
I just wish you were here.
[CLATTERING]
[♪♪♪]
[PHONE BUZZES]
Hello, Mr. Fisk.
I've got the security tapes
from the tunnel right here.
If the kid's out there, I'll find him.
You know me, sir. I don't ever quit.
[♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
♪ Personal insanity, got it like the alley
Turn it up against the rally ♪
♪ You're running it while they're counting
Keepin' score, got the tally ♪
♪ Knock 'em off at the finale
Go, go! ♪
♪ They don't want it, yeah ♪
♪ They don't want it, yeah ♪♪
This is...
- Purple.
- No.
- Blue?
Has anyone heard from Miles?
Look, he's just clearing his head.
I know the kid.
He's got what it takes.
I bet you he's gonna come back through
that door, recharged and ready to fight.
My uncle.
PETER: Hey, where have you been?
My uncle Aaron, he's the Prowler.
PETER: Slow down, Miles.
- He works for Kingpin. He tried to kill me!
This is a pretty hard-core origin story.
It's okay. We're gonna figure it out.
- Were you followed?
- No, I don't think so.
[CLANKING]
[DOORBELL RINGS]
- Cute place. Real homey.
- Oh, great. It's Liv.
I guess I was followed.
Oh, no.
Get out of here, kid.
You messed up bigtime, kid.
Very sloppy.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Let me guess. You're Scorpion.
Well, we're the Spider gang.
Would you mind taking this outside?
NOIR: We don't pick the ballroom,
we just dance.
Ooh, I think I'll be taking that.
[ALL GRUNTING]
Stand, niñito, dale. Prepárate a morir.
MILES:
Aw. Man, stupid pillows.
[♪♪♪]
I said, take it outside!
I got it!
I got this, buddy.
Leave the kid alone!
No, no, no! No!
You gotta go, man.
WOMAN [OVER RADIO]: All vehicles,
we have a disturbance...
...involving multiple Spider... people?
Yeah. On my way.
[SIREN WAILING]
PROWLER:
Give me that thing.
Don't be stupid, kid. Hand it over, now!
Nowhere left to run.
Miles?
Uncle Aaron.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Please, Uncle Aaron.
KINGPIN:
Prowler.
What are you waitin' for? Finish it.
[GUNSHOT]
[KINGPIN GRUNTS]
Get out of here!
[FOOTSTEPS STOMPING ON ROOF]
[AARON PANTING]
No.
Miles.
Uncle Aaron.
This is my fault.
No, Miles.
I'm sorry.
I wanted you to look up to me.
I let you down, man. I let you down.
You're the best of all of us, Miles.
You're on your way.
Just keep going.
[♪♪♪]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER RADIO]
Hands up!
Put your arms up. Now!
Turn around.
Hey! Hey!
Aaron. Aaron, no. No!
All units.
I want an APB on a new Spider-Man.
Hey, bud.
You okay?
We've all been there.
You know, for me...
...it was my Uncle Ben.
For me, it was my Uncle Benjamin.
For me, it was my father.
For me, it was my best friend.
Miles, the hardest thing about this job is...
...you can't always save everybody.
Look, it was my fault.
You wouldn't understand.
Miles, we're probably the only ones
who do understand.
Oh, no.
[HIP-HOP PLAYING
OVER HEADPHONES]
♪ Who in here trying to start a riot? ♪
That way, that way.
Other way, other way,
other way, other way.
Hey there.
Do animals talk in this dimension?
'Cause I don't wanna freak him out.
♪ Brooklyn stand up, stand up
You better just fix your... ♪♪
What's going on?
Bye, Miles.
- Miles, I came to say goodbye.
- We can say goodbye at the collider.
You're not getting it.
You're staying here.
I need to be there.
So you can all go home.
They are going home, Miles.
I'm the only one stayin'.
You're taking my place?
If you stay here, you'll die.
I'm doing what needs to be done.
I just wanted you to hear it from me.
What about MJ?
Not everything works out, kid.
I need the goober.
Please don't make me take it from you.
That's not fair!
You gotta tell them I can do this.
It wasn't their decision.
I gotta make Kingpin pay!
You have to let me make him pay!
Miles, you're gonna get yourself killed.
But I'm ready. I promise!
Then venom-strike me right now.
Or turn invisible on command
so you can get past me.
[GRUNTING]
Look, I know
how much you want this, kid.
NOIR:
Poor little guy.
PETER:
But you don't have it yet.
I'm sorry.
When will I know I'm ready?
You won't. It's a leap of faith.
That's all it is, Miles.
A leap of faith.
[♪♪♪]
[MILES GRUNTING]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
JEFFERSON:
Miles.
Miles, it's your dad.
Please open the door.
Miles, I can see
your shadow movin' around.
Yeah, okay, I get it. I get it.
You're still ignoring me.
Look, can we talk for a minute?
Something...
Something happened to...
Look, sometimes people drift apart, Miles.
And I don't want
that to happen to us, okay?
I know I don't always do what you need
me to do or say what you need me to say.
I see this spark in you.
It's amazing. It's why I push you.
But it's yours.
Whatever you choose to do with it,
you'll be great.
Look, call me when you can. Okay?
I love you.
You don't have to say it back, though.
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪]
[YAWNS]
[BLACKWAY & BLACK CAVIAR'S
"WHAT'S UP DANGER" PLAYING]
♪ 200 miles per hour
With a blindfold on ♪
♪ Mama always asking
"Where did I go wrong?" ♪
Took you long enough.
♪ What's up, danger? ♪
JEFFERSON:
I see this spark in you. It's amazing.
Whatever you choose to do with it,
you'll be great.
RIO:
Our family doesn't run from things.
AARON: You're the best of all of us,
Miles. You're on your way.
Just keep going.
MILES:
When do I know I'm Spider-Man?
PETER:
You won't.
That's all it is, Miles.
A leap of faith.
♪ Like what's up, danger? ♪
♪ Like what's up, danger?
MAY:
Made 'em myself.
They fit perfectly.
- ♪ Can't stop me now ♪
- ♪ Traveled 200 miles ♪
♪ I'm knockin' at your door
And I don't really care ♪
- ♪ If you ain't done wrong ♪
- ♪ I said I got you now ♪
♪ What's up, danger?
Don't be a stranger ♪
♪ I'm right here at your door ♪
♪ I won't leave, I want more ♪
♪ What's up, danger? ♪
♪ Yeah, what's up, danger? ♪
MILES:
Whoo!
- ♪ Can't stop me now ♪
- ♪ I like high chances that I might lose ♪
♪ I like it all on the edge
Just like you, hey ♪
♪ I like tall buildings
So I can leap off of 'em ♪
♪ I go hard with it
No matter how dark it is ♪
♪ Come on, what's up, danger? ♪♪
[ExHALES]
[♪♪♪]
PENI: Kingpin has a private
elevator entrance...
...from his penthouse
to the collider below.
NOIR:
Didn't count on having an audience.
[CHATTERING]
ALL:
You gotta be kidding me.
Thank you. It's nice to be with you
this evening to celebrate Spider-Man.
He and I were very close.
- What a pig.
- I'm right here.
Hold on. Get a load
of how the waiters are dressed.
It's in poor taste, but...
It can't be that easy.
It's that easy.
KINGPIN: I just wanna thank Mary
Jane Parker for being here this evening.
MJ?
Pay attention.
It's not your MJ, Peter, okay?
- I'm sorry, I'll be right back.
- Shh!
Peter! Come here. Trust me. I've
been there. You gotta move on, buddy.
It will take one second. Let me just... Oh!
- Hello.
- Oh, wow.
Um... I just wondered if we could have
some more bread at table 12.
Yeah.
I'm just, uh... I'm really sorry.
Oh! Heh. Don't be sorry. It's just bread.
I wasn't there for you
when you needed me.
- Mm-hm.
- I didn't even try.
That's fine.
You know, I should really get going.
I know I could do better if I just had
another chance to give you, uh...
...the bread that you deserve.
- Are you okay?
- We'll take care of that bread right now.
Well, it's been nice, uh, talking to you.
For you, they should fill this place up
with fresh bread.
- You all right, man?
- Oh, yeah. Totally.
GWEN: Good, 'cause we are not
getting any bread.
[RUMBLING]
KINGPIN: I'm just sorry my family
can't see what we're doing here tonight.
[♪♪♪]
COMPUTER:
Initializing primary ignition sequence.
NOIR:
Sleep.
Start the sequence.
MAN: Uploading Vanessa Fisk
and Richard Fisk DNA sequence.
WOMAN:
Beginning scan for dimensional matches.
[♪♪♪]
COMPUTER:
Secondary ignition in five, four...
...three, two, one.
[GASPS]
[PETER GRUNTS]
Peter, you don't have to stay behind.
I can do it.
It's okay.
I've made up my mind.
I'll put the goober in
and take over the beam.
After you're gone, I'll blow it up.
Good luck, guys.
GWEN:
They know we're here.
[PETER YELLING]
Nice to see you again, Peter.
[NOIR GRUNTING]
PENI:
I got you covered!
These guys are the pits.
[GRUNTS]
Why is this always difficult?
DOC OCK:
Where you going, Peter?
Any last words?
Can I get a minute to think about it?
You have a pen?
Goodbye, Peter Parker.
[♪♪♪]
Who did that?!
- Miles?
- Spider-Man?
- Wow, Miles. You're doing it on command!
- It's about time, right?
PORKER: Look who's here!
GWEN: You figured it out.
- I love you! I am so proud of you!
- Ha, ha, ha.
Do I want kids?
Oh, yeah, I forgot about her.
- Well, that doesn't look promising.
- No, it doesn't.
SCIENTIST:
I've got genetic matches. Hold on.
It's too risky.
Shut up and turn it up.
PETER: On your left!
MILES: On your right!
PETER: I got five o'clock!
Three o'clock! Two o'clock!
Every direction!
Get to a shelter. I'll be right there.
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
[IN ENGLISH]
I tried the school, but I can't get through.
MILES:
Guys, are you seeing this?
GWEN: Looks like our dimensions
are coming to us.
PETER:
Does look cool though, right?
GWEN:
We gotta get back up there.
NOIR: Is that all you got? You gonna fight
or you just bumping gums?
You hard-boiled turtle slapper!
[GASPING]
[GROWLING]
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
[CHUCKLING]
[IN ENGLISH] What are you,
some kind of silly cartoon?
You got a problem with cartoons?
[GRUNTING]
Blammo!
Aww. Did that feel like a cartoon?
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
Gwen!
I like your suit.
Thanks. I made it myself.
PETER: That was adorable, team!
Now, hold on tight!
GWEN: Buckle up, guys.
This is gonna take a while.
[CACKLING]
[HORN HONKS]
All right. Never mind.
Let's end this thing.
Guys, I got it.
I'll go. I'm the one with the goo...
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
Don't watch the mouth.
Watch the hands.
[♪♪♪]
PETER: Miles!
GWEN: Be careful!
Whoo! That was crazy.
We taught him that, right?
I didn't teach him that.
And you definitely didn't.
[♪♪♪]
NOIR:
You okay?
Come on.
Guys, I got control of the beam!
Get up here!
COMPUTER: Alert! Quantum polarity
has been reversed.
[YELLS]
GWEN:
Guess this is it.
Well, nice to know we're not alone.
Right?
GWEN: Yeah.
I got the portal open. You first, Peni.
Thank you, Miles.
From both of us.
I, uh, love you all.
I'm taking this cube thing with me.
I don't understand it.
But I will.
PORKER:
I want you to have this.
It'll fit in your pocket.
That's all, folks.
PETER:
Is he allowed to say that, legally?
Do I get to like the hairdo now?
[CHUCKLES]
You know I'm older than you.
15 months, but it's pretty significant
if you ask me.
Well, Einstein said
time was relative, right?
Heh. Nice.
Friends?
Friends.
Cool.
See you around, Spider-Man.
Your turn.
Yeah, yeah. Right.
You're not going anywhere!
I'll hold him off. You shut this down.
Peter, that wasn't the deal!
Push the green button!
Do not wait for me!
- Ahh! What are you doing?
- You gotta go home!
This guy could kill you!
I can't let Spider-Man die.
Neither can I.
It's okay.
Yeah, it is okay.
You gotta go home, man.
How do I know
I'm not gonna mess it up again?
You won't.
Heh. Right.
It's a leap of faith.
Not bad, kid.
[♪♪♪]
Kingpin!
Nope!
Sorry! That's cheating.
Adiós.
I gotta get to that button.
Oh, no.
Not so easy doing it on your own, is it?
I can't wait to kill one more Spider-Man.
[VANESSA SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
- Where am I?
- What?
Wilson?
Is this what you want, man?
VANESSA: What are you doing?
Vanessa. Vanessa.
- What are we doing here?
- I don't know, Richard.
It's me. You know me.
VANESSA:
We're leaving now.
Don't go.
Stay with me.
Please!
You're not stopping this. Not today.
I am stopping this. Right now!
I need backup.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO]
[GRUNTING]
Come on.
The real Spider-Man
couldn't even beat me.
You're nothing!
You took my family.
And now I'm gonna make sure
you never see yours again.
[YELLS]
[♪♪♪]
Get up, Spider-Man.
Get up! Come on!
[GRUNTS]
Come on. Come on. Come on.
[♪♪♪]
I'll always have my family.
You ever hear of the shoulder touch?
What?
[IN DEEP VOICE]
Hey.
[IN NORMAL VOICE] Hey, Kingpin!
Push the green button for me!
[GRUNTING]
[♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
[JEFFERSON COUGHING]
[SIRENS WAILING]
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Miles? Miles? Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
You're probably busy...
No! I can talk, I can talk.
Look, so I came by earlier because, uh...
- Your uncle...
- I know, Dad.
I am so sorry.
Yeah.
Do you know who did it?
I thought I did.
But I was wrong.
Look, Miles, what I said at the door...
...it wasn't just talk.
Look, you know, I was thinking
maybe we could find a nice wall...
...privately owned,
like at the police station...
...and you could, um, "throw up"
some of your art.
Man, I'm bad at this.
Okay, Miles. Miles? You there?
Oh, come on, man. C-Mobile!
- [IN DEEP VOICE] Officer.
- Spider-Man!
Listen, um, down there, that was...
I mean, I owe you...
Okay!
[CLEARS THROAT]
I look forward to workin' with you.
Heh, heh. Yeah, me, too. I guess.
I don't approve of your methods...
...but we're just gonna have
to agree to disagree.
Thank you for your bravery tonight.
- I love you.
- Heh, heh.
Wait, what?
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
And look behind you!
[♪♪♪]
[CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING]
All right. Cool. Yeah.
- Thanks, Spider-Man.
- Spider-Man, a su servicio. Thank you.
Hey, man. What's up, little man?
MAN: New Spider-Man.
Yeah. Yeah, I'm the new Spider-Man.
Check it out.
Whoa!
That was part of the move.
Okay, let's do this one last time, yeah?
For real this time. This is it.
My name is Miles Morales.
I was bitten by a radioactive spider.
And for like two days, I've been
the one and only Spider-Man.
I think you know the rest.
I finished my essay.
Saved a bunch of people.
- Got hit by a drone.
- Ouch!
I did this with my dad.
Met my roommate. Finally.
Slapped a sticker
where my dad's never gonna find it.
And when I feel alone, like no one
understands what I'm going through...
...I remember my friends who get it.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
I never thought
I'd be able to do any of this stuff.
But I can.
Anyone can wear the mask.
You could wear the mask.
If you didn't know that before,
I hope you do now.
'Cause I'm Spider-Man.
And I'm not the only one.
Not by a long shot.
♪ Needless to say
I keep her in check ♪
♪ She was all bad-bad, nevertheless ♪
♪ Callin' it quits now
Baby, I'm a wreck ♪♪
GWEN:
Miles. Miles!
You got a minute?
[♪♪♪]
♪ Stepped out of my zone ♪
♪ I had to get out all alone ♪
♪ And figure it out on my own ♪
♪ And I know what I really want now ♪
♪ Can't stop me, can't break me ♪
♪ What don't kill me gon' make me ♪
♪ Shoot for the stars, no safety
And now I see clear in HD ♪
♪ Gotta go hard
Gotta go hard ♪
♪ I ain't got time to waste
I ain't got time ♪
♪ I gotta go high
Gotta go high ♪
♪ I gotta elevate
I gotta elevate ♪
♪ They wanna fight
They wanna fight ♪
♪ I'm just gon' let 'em hate
I'm just gon' let 'em hate ♪
♪ I gotta go high
Gotta go high ♪
♪ I gotta elevate
I gotta elevate ♪
♪ You gotta choose a side
You gotta choose a side ♪
♪ You better keep
You better do what's right ♪
♪ Or you gonna lose the fight ♪
♪ Gotta go hard ♪
♪ Gotta choose a side
I'm gon' let 'em hate ♪
♪ You better
Gotta go high ♪
♪ You better do what's right
I gotta elevate ♪
♪ Heroes never die ♪
♪ I'm a web slinger
To a gunslinger ♪
♪ No millimeter
This is my arena ♪
♪ I'm the black widow
With the best stinger ♪
♪ And I'll make you scream
Like a bad singer ♪
♪ I'm everything that you
Wanna be plus more ♪
♪ Since there's no heroes anymore ♪
♪ Jump out the window
Him with the mask on ♪
♪ Who the bad man
That our man gotta bash on? ♪
♪ Oh, we'll never link up
Blink and you will see us ♪
♪ Young prince 'bout to ink up
See me in the NYC ♪
♪ You can never swing by me ♪
♪ Oh, we'll never link up
Blink and you will see us ♪
♪ Young prince 'bout to ink up
See me in the NYC ♪
♪ Home of the B.I.G., yo ♪
♪ They just slander me
I just plan to be ♪
♪ Something powerful for my family ♪
♪ Tried to balance life
And my sanity ♪
♪ Show a different side of humanity ♪
♪ So amazing, keep upraising ♪
♪ Save you from a home invasion ♪
♪ Chasing robbers from the bank ♪
♪ You facing friendly
Neighborhood Spider-Man ♪
♪ Gotta go hard ♪
♪ I ain't got time to waste
I ain't got time ♪
♪ I gotta go high
Gotta go high ♪
♪ I gotta elevate
I gotta elevate ♪
♪ They wanna fight
They wanna fight ♪
♪ I'm just gon' let 'em hate
I'm just gon' let 'em hate ♪
♪ I gotta go high
Gotta go high ♪
♪ I gotta elevate
I gotta elevate ♪
♪ Okay, I fight crime
Through the nighttime ♪
♪ When the lights shine, I go python ♪
♪ I'm falling on my last lifeline ♪
♪ There's no way in my right mind ♪
♪ My city up on my back tight ♪
♪ How can I possibly act right? ♪
♪ I'm Robin Hood, I'm the black knight ♪
♪ I know you heard 'bout my last fight ♪
♪ 'Cause I win over and over again ♪
♪ Battling evil, I'm hoping to win ♪
♪ Fighting my demons
I'm nice for a reason ♪
♪ Enticed with the bleeding
I'm showing my sins ♪
♪ How can you expect me to stay sane? ♪
♪ Protect me
My technique go X speed ♪
♪ On highways and Jet Skis ♪
♪ Look, I ain't got no time
To be hanging around nobody ♪
♪ Trying to figure out
If they good or evil ♪
♪ I'm fighting the crime
Saving your lives ♪
♪ One at a time, I'm killing the rhymes
I do it for the people ♪
♪ I'm Peter Parker
Running through The Six ♪
♪ With a bag full of tricks, my boy
You better choose a side ♪
♪ I may have lost the battle
But I will not lose the war ♪
♪ I can promise you
I will not lose this time ♪
♪ I did it all independent, no
Really, y'all, independent ♪
♪ Now we winning
I got my homeys ♪
♪ Cooking up in the kitchen
Intuition say ♪
♪ We gon' have to win
And give us the business ♪
♪ The world is mine and you
Gon' have to pay me attention ♪
♪ And I did everything
That I did on my own ♪
♪ I'm the only one for real
There can never be a clone ♪
♪ Better talk to me nice
Better watch your tone ♪
♪ And I'm putting on for my home slice ♪
♪ So I gotta go hard ♪
♪ I gotta elevate
I gotta elevate ♪♪
[♪♪♪]
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
We on the way up ♪
♪ I went from boy to a man, wow
Opposition had to stand down ♪
♪ And I had to make a perfect plan
Now I'm on the wave ♪
♪ I had to fight for the city
I had to fight for the people ♪
♪ You gotta do what all leaders do ♪
♪ Everyone here, we believe in you
Know you can be a hero ♪
♪ 'Cause we see you do it
And this is the time that we needin' you ♪
♪ Everyone is here to see you move ♪
♪ Winnin', we winnin', we winnin' ♪
♪ We put a world on a wave ♪
♪ And every time
You swinging through the city ♪
♪ You are saving the day ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
We on the way up ♪
♪ We had to fight for the town
Now there's no villains allowed ♪
♪ Everyone cheer in the crowd
But I'm still way up, I'm over the clouds ♪
♪ We had to fight for the city
Competition was lethal ♪
♪ Honestly, it's no biggie
I had to do what all leaders do ♪
♪ Uh-oh, they don't want it man
Uh-oh, they don't want it, I promise ♪
Uh-oh, they can't handle my problems ♪
♪ They always hate on us
But they can't do it without us ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
We out here cleanin' the streets ♪
♪ We don't accept the defeat
We keep on going until we win ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
All of 'em weak in the knees ♪
♪ Deer in headlights when they freeze ♪
♪ But we keep on going on until we win ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
We on the way up ♪
We on the way up ♪♪
[♪♪♪]
♪ This morning I woke up in a fortress
Of distortion ♪
♪ I'm at war with my emotions
I'm at war with, they force me ♪
♪ Trying to fight for what's right
And got sidetracked ♪
♪ Where your mind at?
Never mind that ♪
♪ Can't be thinking or blinking
You swim or you sink ♪
♪ When you leaving it
Load them out, whip it ♪
♪ I stay with my brethren
I pray for a chick, my prey in my sights ♪
♪ So I'm doing what's right
And I'm asking no questions ♪
♪ I wanna be home free
Where's one that was lonely? ♪
♪ But I'm ready and waiting
For my day of salvation ♪
♪ And I'm patient ♪
♪ I'm coming home now ♪
♪ I'm coming home ♪
♪ Right where I belong now ♪
♪ Right where I belong ♪
♪ They're looking for saviors
I'm looking for safety ♪
♪ They're never gonna break me
Take me ♪
♪ Down to my knees
Believe I'm never gonna beg ♪
♪ Or plead, I never say never
But I guarantee ♪
♪ Gather my strength
Goin' hard in the paint ♪
♪ Paint you all pictures
Put on display ♪
♪ I'm gonna get it
I give, then I take ♪
♪ Can't take me down now ♪
♪ My feet on the ground now ♪
♪ Fight till I'm down now ♪
♪ Say it out loud now ♪
♪ Say it out loud
Are you ready for war? ♪
♪ I'm coming home now ♪
♪ I'm coming home ♪
♪ Right where I belong now ♪
♪ Right where I belong ♪♪
[♪♪♪]
♪ Oh, Spidey-bells
Spidey-bells ♪
♪ Swinging through Midtown ♪
♪ Oh, what fun to sling a web ♪
♪ And take the bad guys down ♪
♪ Spidey-bells, Spidey-bells ♪
♪ Quipping all the time ♪
♪ Oh, what fun to swing around ♪
♪ New York while fighting crime ♪
♪ Swinging through the streets ♪
♪ On a web of spider silk ♪
♪ Kicking all the butts ♪
♪ Of villains and their ilk ♪
♪ Bombs from Goblins fling
Fling! ♪
♪ Pumpkins blooming bright
Bright! ♪
♪ How hard it is to consistently bring
Peace to New York all night ♪
♪ Oh, Spidey-bells, might be swell ♪
♪ To do more than fight crime ♪
♪ I got a lot of qualities
That don't get much airtime ♪
♪ I can sing, I can dance
I tell jokes, I act ♪
♪ I'd get big, big...
Big deal if my agent called me back ♪
♪ Why did I agree
To do this stupid song? ♪
♪ I have a degree ♪
♪ In chemical engineering ♪♪
[♪♪♪]
You're a bit late.
MAN: We can't all be everywhere at once.
Little text might've been nice.
MAN: I was gone for less than two hours.
What happened?
Okay. I know what it looks like.
- But here's the good news.
- Oh, here we go.
The multiverse didn't collapse.
- Oh, cool!
- Little touch and go.
But it worked out.
- Great story. Did you finish the goober?
- It's not a goober. It's a gizmo.
MAN: Do you always have to call me out?
It's just really frustrating and bums me out.
WOMAN:
Don't get excited, Miguel.
It's just a prototype.
MIGUEL: Not excited.
WOMAN: But you could be the first person
to make an autonomous multiverse jump.
Or the last.
So we're just gonna roll the dice on this?
So, what you do you say, pal?
Where you want to go first?
Let's start at the beginning one last time.
Earth '67.
[♪♪♪]
Whoa! What the...?
I'm Spider-Man.
- I need you to come with me.
- Who the heck are you?
I just told you...
Listen. I'm from the future.
- How dare you point at me!
- You were pointing first.
- It's rude to point.
- You're being very rude.
Which one pointed first?
Spider-Man pointed first. Obviously.
- You're pointing at me right now.
- I'm not pointing.
Look at your finger.
I'm pointing out your pointing,
which is different.
You haven't seen pointing.
You're accusing me
of pointing while you're...!
[♪♪♪]